ECAFLIP'S SCRATCHING POST
Don't worry. Your dad always wins.
Before, maybe...
He wouldn't like hearing that.
Even though he's got his arm back,
he hasn't fought for years.
I think he's lost his warrior spirit...
You're wrong.
He has fighting in his blood.
It's just that with Eva, you and Flopin,
his priorities have changed.
It was best to leave him alone.
He can focus on his fight.
Maybe you are right.
You two would make good parents.
Wait!
I can't go on.
I'm too old for... Well, you know.
We're almost there.
You keep saying that.
There's no end to this staircase.
And Ruel, he hates endless staircases.
Ruel...
I'm way too old for this, Yugo.
I just can't. I'm too old,
too bald, too weak,
basically two teeth...
Just leave me here.
Ruel!
A Kama?
A shiny Kama. I might give it to you
if you stop whining.
Whining?
You could show me a bit more respect!
Do you have more?
Yes. You'll get them
if you stop complaining.
That's what princesses do.
Don't steal my lines.
Okay.
I'm not as rich as you,
but, as a princess, I have some savings.
Stop whining and it'll be yours.
Do I look like a complainer?
I think we've arrived.
I reckon it's the Ecaflip Temple.
Yes. I've told you
how his guardian, Ush,
half-brother to Kerub and Atcham,
a big gambler, almost got us in Ecaflip.
I suppose we go in through that...
...cat door?
If we must, boys first.
I'll go.
My arthrosis is acting up again!
At my age, I... Hmm?
At my age, everything's fine!
What have we got? Oh.
It looks like...
...a giant training room!
Whose idea was this?
Don't stand there staring. Give me a hand!
Make an effort!
Don't blame us for your big butt.
Don't laugh too hard.
If you get your mother's--
Easy, girls.
I'll go to the other side to push.
What?
No, wait...
Yugo...
How dare you?
I was just helping.
By putting your hand on my...?
My bottom! I'm the princess of the--
A princess in my temple! I'm honored!
Ush!
Yugo recognized me, flattering.
How have you been?
Fine. You know why we're here.
And you won't make it easy for us.
All right! You know I love to gamble.
Losing our last game
still sticks in my gut.
It's haunting me. I'd never lost before.
No time! Our friends need us.
They are safe.
We're the good guys.
I'm sick of hearing that.
You're a bunch of nut-jobs!
No, Mama!
Give me back my family!
Elely!
She's like her father!
You're the one Oropo wants
for an Iop goddess... Why not?
You have a lot to learn!
Stop rushing without thinking!
As for you...
What?
No super-Eliatrope-powers here.
An inhibitor!
Like in Justice's prison.
Yeah, that sucks.
We'll see how you do without your powers.
The rules are simple.
You're on my scratching post.
If you want out, you have to get this key.
I'm not sure what you think
you're defending, but I beg you...
You're not very convincing.
I'll teach you how to really beg.
There's time.
Rest a little.
How can I sleep, Echo?
Everything is falling into place.
I've been waiting for this for centuries.
You've never been so impatient.
Don't worry. We'll support you to the end.
-Can I ask you something?
-Yes?
You've followed me from the beginning.
Do you believe in my cause or...
-Or?
-It's just out of love?
Interesting question.
A bit of both, I think.
But I believed in your cause first.
That must mean something.
And the others?
Do they do it for the cause,
or out of love?
Do you know
that your sense of humor is wicked?
I know, I try. They adore and respect you.
How many truly believe in the plan?
They believe in you. It's the same thing.
Not quite.
Ush! Stop playing around!
I can't hear you. You're too far!
Not even trying!
Spread out. I'll bring him.
Cut off all the exits!
I've got the center.
Okay. Better get going.
Give me that key!
How's it going?
Ush is playing with them.
Like a cat with a mouse.
Is all this really useful?
The best way to get to know someone
is to fight them.
What's the point? I can wipe them out.
You know that this isn't goal.
We need your brother.
You already know what I think.
You will never convince Yugo.
I don't need to convince him.
That's not the problem, Adamai.
Part of you wants to see them win.
True... And I have no idea why.
Don't feel guilty.
They are endearing,
and fundamentally good.
Oropo! It's happening more often.
Don't worry. It'll be fine.
-Are you a little off?
-Let me get my bearings.
Have a nice trip!
Oops?
Yugo!
You're just too cute!
Ow!
Nasty beast!
Amalia...
It's terrible! They're so cute!
Get off him!
The Brotherhood of the Tofu
taken down by kittens. How pathetic!
No tickling!
We never get bored with you, my friends.
Little fool!
You protected me.
Really?
Yes. Don't take me for a fool.
I would never do that. Huh?
Here, kitty, kitty! Come to Daddy Ruel.
Hi, kitties. Oh, yes, pretty kitties.
Come and play with Daddy Ruel.
Who's the toy-toy for?
Kitty-kitty!
I'm the one.
-You all right?
-Yes, nothing serious.
Ready for round two?
With pleasure, Yugo!
Are you hurt?
-No.
-Then why aren't you moving?
Give me back my Kama...
It's about honor, right?
I saved you earlier and, as a true Iop,
something inside you says you owe me.
-Really?
-No.
It's a wondrous thing,
don't you think, brother?
Seeing that little girl realizing
what honor really is.
With Eva and Percedal,
it was bound to happen.
You won't win this fight.
Without his powers, it's uneven.
I have an idea!
Catch!
Are you sure this'll work, Elely?
No! But it wouldn't be any fun otherwise.
Here, your friends like Kamas.
You cheated!
Not more than you.
Well played.
I lost again, but it really was great fun.
We really should talk someday.
You know honor. Why are you here?
Soon, you'll understand it all.
There is a time for everything.
Watch your backs with your next opponent.
Papa would like Ush.